bentenblog.com 2019-05-23

# PRIVACY POLICY - BENTENBLOG

**At  www.bentenblog.com** we value the privacy of our visitors and with this privacy policy want to alert them on the information we collect and how their are been used.

We are not responsible for republished content from this blog on other blogs or websites without our permission.

**Do we collect information?**

Yes, we do collect information from you.

**What information do we collect from you?**

Anytime you sign up on this blog, subscribe to our newsletter or, fill any form that asks for information, we collect information from you. When subscribing or signing up in our blog, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your: name, email address, and so on.

Also, we collect information when you visit our site via web stats programs. We collect technical information such as your IP address, web browser, location, and other information.

**Do we use your information?**

Yes, we do.

**What do we use the information for?**

There are ways we use information collect from you. Observe the ways below:

  *  To improve this blog.
  *  To send you periodic emails (Optional).
  *  So as to personalize your experience.
  * To administer survey or other site features.

**Do we protect your information?**

Yes.

#### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement some web security measures to maintain the safety of your information. However, these measures are not totally safe since hack and breaches in security are common on the net.

**Do we disclose your information to outside parties?**

We may disclose it when we believe that doing so is appropriate. Some of the occasions might be to comply with the law, enforce our site policy or to protect the right of others.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act:**

This blog posts and services are directed to students in particle, non students are welcome too. It is open to people who are 13 years old or above.

**Linking to other websites:**

On occasions, we may link to other sites. These other sites have their separate privacy policies. We take no responsibility for the other content and activities of the linked sites.

USE OF COOKIES

www.bentenblog.com does not use cookies on their website.  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies, web beacons and Ip addresses of visitors on our site to render ads directly.  
Some ads may be displayed on this site by third party companies and the display of such ads is not controlled by www.bentenblog.com but by the third party ads servers.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [**www.bentenblog.com**](https://www.bentenblog.com/).  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [**www.bentenblog.com**](https://www.bentenblog.com/) and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
****

[**www.bentenblog.com**](https://www.bentenblog.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
The add server companies and websites  will be published here thereafter so you should consult their respective privacy policies  for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

[**www.bentenblog.com**](https://www.bentenblog.com/)’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the specific browsers’ websites.

This privacy policy is subject to change without prior notice to visitors and are kindly advised to always check this page as it can be updated at any time.

This privacy policy was last updated on June 6th, 2018.

If you have any questions you can freely contact me directly through my personal email address at: [benjaminanyigor@gmail.com](mailto:benjaminanyigor@gmail.com) .
